- OH BOY!
YOU SAID YOUR PHONE
WAS BROKEN
JUST FORGOT TO CHARGE IT
WHOLE OUTFIT YOU’RE WEARING
GOD I HOPE IT’S IRONIC
DID YOU JUST SAY
YOU’RE FINISHED?
DIDN’T KNOW WE STARTED
IT’S ALL JUST SO FAMILIAR
BABY, WHAT DO YOU CALL IT?
STUPID
OR IS IT
SLOW?
MAYBE IT’S
USELESS?
BUT THERE’S A CUTER WORD
FOR IT
I KNOW
MANCHILD
WHY YOU ALWAYS COME
A RUNNING TO ME?
FUCK MY LIFE
WON’T YOU LET AN INNOCENT
WOMAN BE?
NEVER HEARD OF SELF CARE
HALF YOUR BRAIN
JUST AINT THERE
MANCHILD
WHY YOU ALWAYS
COME A RUNNING
TAKING ALL MY LOVING
FROM ME?
WHY SO SEXY
IF SO DUMB?
AND HOW SURVIVE
THE EARTH SO LONG?
IF I’M NOT THERE
IT WON’T GET DONE
I CHOOSE TO BLAME YOUR MOM
MANCHILD
WHY YOU ALWAYS COME
A RUNNING TO ME?
FUCK MY LIFE
WON’T YOU LET AN INNOCENT
WOMAN BE?
NEVER HEARD OF SELF CARE
HALF YOUR BRAIN
JUST AINT THERE
MANCHILD
WHY YOU ALWAYS
COME A RUNNING
TAKING ALL MY LOVING
FROM ME?
OH I LIKE MY BOYS PLAYING
HARD TO GET
AND I LIKE MY MEN
ALL INCOMPETENT
AND I SWEAR THEY CHOOSE ME
I’M NOT CHOOSING THEM
AMEN
HEY MEN!
OH, I LIKE MY BOYS PLAYING
HARD TO GET
AND I LIKE MY MEN
ALL INCOMPETENT
AND I SWEAR THEY CHOOSE ME
I’M NOT CHOOSING THEM
AMEN
(AMEN)
HEY MEN!
HEY MEN!)
MANCHILD
WHY YOU ALWAYS COME
A RUNNING TO ME?
(ALWAYS COME A RUNNING
TO ME)
FUCK MY LIFE
WON’T YOU LET AN INNOCENT
WOMAN BE?
OH, I LIKE MY BOYS PLAYING
HARD TO GET
AND I LIKE MY MEN
ALL INCOMPETENT
AND I SWEAR THEY CHOOSE ME
I’M NOT CHOOSING THEM
AMEN
HEY MEN!
(HEY MEN!)